<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-11-17T16:05:33+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Developer Community TLV</title><subtitle>The place to get info about the leading dev communities in TLV.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Sponsor</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/09/17/sponsor.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sponsor" /><published>2020-09-17T00:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2020-09-17T00:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/09/17/sponsor</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/09/17/sponsor.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;sponsor&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#SPONSOR&quot;&gt;SPONSOR&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is only &lt;strong&gt;ONE SPONSORSHIP TIER&lt;/strong&gt; for the event, &lt;strong&gt;COMMUNITY SPONSOR&lt;/strong&gt; for $1000 (USD).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-package&quot;&gt;The Package&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One&lt;/strong&gt; 5-minute ignite talk in the Sponsored Track.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Logo on event sponsor page, and a social media mention.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Link to sponsor page in newsletter and other communications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;more-info&quot;&gt;More Info&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;All ignites are subject to approval by the content moderation team.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There are approximately ~40 slots available - ~8-10 slots an hour (allowing for some chit chat, Q&amp;amp;A and lead time between sessions).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sponsorship is on first come, first served basis (pending the signing of the contract) to select your time slot.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will allow one slot per company, companies interested in more than one slot will be added to a waitlist that will be opened up by order of request.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sponsors will not receive any contact or event lists for GDPR and privacy reasons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">SPONSOR There is only ONE SPONSORSHIP TIER for the event, COMMUNITY SPONSOR for $1000 (USD).</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/pic01.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/pic01.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Code of Conduct</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/code-of-conduct.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Code of Conduct" /><published>2020-09-15T00:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2020-09-15T00:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/code-of-conduct</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/code-of-conduct.html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;code-of-conduct&quot;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our community is dedicated to providing a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), or technology choices. We do not tolerate harassment of community participants in any form. Sexual language and imagery is not appropriate for any community venue, including Discord, channels, talks, workshops, parties, Twitter, and other online media. Community participants violating these rules may be sanctioned or expelled at the discretion of the conference moderators or event organizers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harassment includes offensive verbal or written comments related to gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion, technology choices, sexual images in public spaces, deliberate intimidation, stalking, following, harassing photography or recording, sustained disruption of talks or other events, inappropriate physical contact, and unwelcome sexual attention. Participants asked to stop any harassing behavior are expected to comply immediately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are being harassed, notice that someone else is being harassed, or have any other concerns, please contact a member of the staff (event organizer or moderator) immediately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staff are identified with a separate role in the online forum (event organizer or moderator). Staff will be happy to help participants contact experiencing harassment to feel safe for the duration of their participation in our community. We value your participation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We expect participants to follow these rules in all community-related media, including Discord, YouTube, Twitter, or any other online presence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Code of Conduct is based on https://confcodeofconduct.com/.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Code of Conduct</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/pic07.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/pic07.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>